

# DANIYAL SALEEM

#### ASSISTANT MANAGER



Male



20-April-2001



+923058406026 - +923400209926



daniyalsaleemqureshi@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniyal-saleem-

417b31287



Elite Town Housing Scheme Ferozpur Road

Lahore

## **SKILLS**

#### Language:

English, Urdu, Punjabi

#### Computer:

Word, Excel, Oracle, Inpage, Visio

#### Passport:

MF5758001

#### **Driving Licence:**

LE-21-21841(LTV)

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

Hi! This is Daniyal Saleem. 3+ years of diverse experience in Home Textile and Denim Sector. My years of experience in different and famous organizations like Nishat Apparel Ltd, Western Global Services, Generation Brand and Gree Service Center Ltd. have given me the valuable recourse to impart practical knowledge in the area of process improvement and management. I have the flexibility to change the decision according to the circumstances for the betterment of the work field and to adopt the any environment. I've great command over teamwork, public speaking. Specialities in:-° Time, motion, capacity and Production Studies. Pre/Post Costing. Man power planing as per product. Piece rate calculation (Wages Preparation). Layout planning and execute. Store Manage.

## **OBJECTIVE**

To secure a challenging position in a reputable organization to expand my learnings, knowledge, and skills.

## **EDUCATION**

#### University of Punjab (PU)

Associate Degree in Arts (B.A.)

2020 - 2022

Got 61% Marks

#### Govt.Islamia College Civil Lines (GICCL)

FSC Pre.Engineering

2017 - 2019

Got 59% Marks

#### **Govt.Centeral Model School Lower Mall.**

Matric in Computer Science

2015 - 2017

Got 76% Marks

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **GENERATION (Pvt.) LTD**

(Assistant Manager IE) Q.A, development & implementation of ORACLE AND APEX

2021 - Now

- Daily RMS Verification.
- New Style Layout as per requirement.
- · Machine arrangement as per new style.
- Time, method & capacity study of new style/operations
- · Sampling weekly payment.
- Production payment including CMT
- Oracle Q.A and implement In Departments.

## Nishat Apparel Unit II (2 years)

I.E Officer

2018 - 2021

- Daily RMS Verification.
- Daily NPT.
- Style Bulletin & Rate Finalization with consent of Production. Search & Find Old references in case of Conflict.
- New Style Layout as per requirement.
- · Machine arrangement as per new style.
- · Daily WIP Status making & follow up.
- Daily PO closing submission to accounts.
- Time, method & capacity study of new style/operations
- $\bullet$  Follow up of submitted checklist to accounts by clerks.
- Problems/issues of checklists is verified & resolved.Extra work of skipped operation in case of already approved operations.

## **REFERENCES**

Reference Will Be Furnished On Demand.

• Memo in case of operation that is not already approved in that style.

### Western Global Services (8 month)

Store Keeper 2017 - 2018

- Maintain Stock
- Daily Segregation Report
- Daily Stock Issuance Report
- Demand New Stock
- Meal Sheet Clearance

## **Gree Service Center DWP GROUP (6 month)**

Ac Technician Helper 2017 - 2017

- Overall service Ac (1 Ton to 4 Ton) & Dispenser Also
- Compressor Change
- Vacuum & Charge Gas
- Cleaning Inner & Outer Assembly By Flushing Method